gerberlife.com 2011-05-09

# Privacy Notice

Please take a moment to read the following Privacy Notice. You do not need to call us or do anything as a result of this notice. It is meant to inform you of some important information about our privacy policy and your rights. **If we make changes to this Privacy Notice, we will post them here and update the date set forth below. If any changes we make are material, we may take additional measures to inform you of those changes. Use of this website signifies your agreement with our privacy policy.**

#### **Our Information Confidentiality and Security Policy**

Our most important asset is our customers’ trust. We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to protect your nonpublic personal financial information. We permit only authorized persons who are trained in the proper handling of customer information to have access to that information. Gerber Life does not sell customer information to marketing, mailing list or telemarketing companies. 

#### **Information We May Collect**

We may collect nonpublic personal financial information about you from the following sources: 

  * From your insurance application, information such as your name, address and telephone number; 
  * From third parties, such as claims, consumer or medical reports; 
  * From your transactions with us, information such as your premium payment and claim history. 

#### **Use and Disclosure**

We do not disclose any nonpublic personal financial information about our customers or former customers to anyone, except to certain third parties who perform services on our behalf and as permitted by law.

#### **General**

This notice pertains to data collected from you when you use our website. Please refer to “Our Information Confidentiality and Security Policy” regarding data collected when you apply to Gerber Life for insurance.

Many of the ways in which you interact with the Gerber Life internet site allow us to learn about you. We collect and store statistics and other information about the online activities of our visitors on an aggregated (collective) basis. For example, we track the number of people who view each page to learn which features are the most popular.

In those instances where we do collect personally identifiable information, you have the option of choosing whether or not to reveal it to us. Some examples of when you voluntarily submit this kind of information include a request by you for information or submitting an application for insurance, providing feedback to us in connection with our website or registering for our internet newsletter. Personally identifiable information you may choose to provide can include your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address and other information you may wish to tell us. If you do not provide all “required” information, however, some portions of our site will not work properly for you, or you may be denied access to certain sections of the Web site.

#### **How We Use And Disclose Your Information**

We do not sell your email addresses or your name and personal demographic information to mass marketers or other third parties. We use your information to do such things as distribute email communications, operate our site, enhance our site, and sell and deliver advertising. We also use this data, both aggregated and personally identifiable, to enhance your on-site experience by displaying content and marketing messages that we believe will be of interest to you. We may disclose information from our site, on an aggregated or non-personally idenitifiable basis, to third parties for purposes of analyzing our Web site traffic and optimizing how we lay out content on the site.

#### **Cookies And Other Tracking Methods**

Cookies are small pieces of information stored on your hard drive, not on our Site. We use cookies, or, in a limited number of cases, IP addresses, for a number of reasons. First, cookies allow you to store your password without having to constantly re-enter it. Second, cookies can help us tailor our Site or a marketing message to better match your needs and interests. Third, cookies allow us to better understand how users use our Site, which in turn helps us focus our resources on features that are most popular with our users. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, but some parts of our site may not work properly if you do.

We use a third party service provider to serve ads on our behalf on our Site. They may collect anonymous information about your visits to our Web site, and your interaction with our products and services. They may also use information about your visits to our Site and other Web sites to target advertisements for our products. Anonymous information is collected on our Web Site through the use of a pixel call. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this anonymous information used, please visit [www.networkadvertising.org/consumer/opt_out.asp](http://www.networkadvertising.org/consumer/opt_out.asp). You can opt out of having your anonymous information collected by our service provider by visiting <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>. If you select the “opt out” button there, our service provider will delete cookies related to this service and try to place a new cookie that instructs them not to track your future activities when they detect that cookie. If your browsers are configured to reject cookies when you visit the opt-out page, our service provider cannot set a no-track cookie. Also, if you subsequently erase your cookies, use a different computer or change web browsers, you will need to opt-out again.

#### **Other Sites**

Please note that if you provide any information on your own to parties who provide services to us or to any other sites you encounter on the Internet (even if these sites display our branding), different rules may apply to their use or disclosure of the personal information you disclose to them. We encourage you to investigate and ask questions before disclosing information to third parties.

#### **Limits On Our Abilities**

We do not disclose personally identifiable information about users of our website to anyone, except as noted herein or permitted by law.

#### **Security**

We maintain electronic and procedural safeguards to protect personally identifiable information.  We permit only authorized persons who are trained in the proper handling of personally identifiable information to have access to that information.

#### **Changes To Web Site**

We may change, move or delete portions of, or may add to, our site from time to time.

IPVY-01(051)
